Guide to A. George Schillinger Papers RG.048
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
A. George Schillinger Papers
1946-2008
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Schillinger, A. George, 1930
RG.048
20 Linear Feet
Biographical / Historical
Professor A. George Schillinger was born in Hungary in 1930. He began his career at the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn in 1957 where he was chairman of Polytechnic's division of management, creator and director of the Executive MS in the Management of Technology Program, and editor of the Journal of Technology in Society. Schillinger received his B.S. in Electrical Engineering from City College of New York and his M.S. and Doctor of Engineering Science from Columbia University.
Scope and Contents
The A. George Schillinger Papers contain documents from 1946 to 2008. These documents were assembled by Schillinger throughout his academic and professional careers at Brooklyn Poly (operating under the names of Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn (1900-1973), Polytechnic Institute of New York (1973-1985), Polytechnic University (1985-2008), Polytechnic Institute of New York University) and Columbia University. Most documents are of significance to Polytechnic departments and programs, the American Society for Macro-Engineering, and Technology in Society. Documents include correspondence, curricula, information on committees, financials, and more. The collection is 20 linear feet, located on bay 29, shelves 2F-7F and 2E-4E.
Arrangement
This collection is housed in seventeen boxes and arranged into six series:
Series I: Academia, 1946-2008 Series II: The American Society for Macro-Engineering, 1981-2005 Series III: Industrial Research Institute, 1978-1983 Series IV: Management of Technology, 1987-2007 Series V: Brooklyn Poly, 1949-2008 Series VI: Societies, Conferences, and Committees, 1968-2002
Original order was maintained whenever possible. However, there was some reorganization of materials for series placement.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was donated to the Poly Archives by the Technology Management and Innovation Department of NYU Tandon in 2022.
Polytechnic University (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.).; Technology; Management; Engineering
- Series I: Academia, 1946-2008
  - Sub-series A: Columbia University, 1951-1959
    - EE293 Columbia, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Columbia Homework, Quizzes, Exams, 1951-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - EE306: Advanced Network Theory (Columbia), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - EE305: Advanced Network Theory (Columbia), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - EE208 Columbia, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Columbia Homework & Exams, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sub-series B: Coursework and Notes, 1946-1969
    - El. Mag. Theory - Wavelengths - Antennae (EE265/66), 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Vector Analysis (208), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - L162.07 - Transistors, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 205 Zadeh: Ntwk Analysis & Lees' Notes, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 206 Zadeh: Ntwk Synthesis, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Communication Theory Course Notes, undated (Box 1, Item 1)
    - E.E. L145 Laboratory Experiment Instructions, 1949 (Box 1, Item 2)
    - Notes for Mathematical Statistics 103, 1954 (Box 1, Item 3)
    - IE 613 Linear Programming Notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - R-130 R-161 Notes & Quizes, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - IE 941 Course Outline, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Eitel-McCullough 2000T Triode, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - R-162 Notes B, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - R-162 Quizes, Problems, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - ASH: Coding Lectures, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Sub-series C: Drafts, Papers, and Publications, 1969-2004
    - Encyclopedia of Science, Technology, and Ethics, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - David L. Bodde (Lighting the Way Report), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Helen Hockney Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Inzelt Annamaria, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Anthony R. Michaelis, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Technology Review (1987) (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Technology & Culture, 1969-1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence on "Technology Forecast for 1980", 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Institute of International Education, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Reddy, Srinivas K., undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Sub-series D: Fellowships, 1996-2005
    - Diebold Institute Fellowship, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Jewish Historical Society Book Review, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Requests to European Sources, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - U.S. Fellowship Candidates, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Requests for Case Suggestions, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Application Project Proposal and Resume, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The Diebold Institute Fellowship Applications 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The Diebold Institute Fellowship Applications 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Diebold, John, 1996-2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Diebold Institute for Public Policy Studies, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Diebold Institute Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Diebold Institute - Private Financing of Public Infrastructure, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Diebold/Deutsche Bk Monograph Draft, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Soros Foundation, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Paul and Daisy Soros Fellowships 2005 Selection, 2005-01-20 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - Sub-series E: Nominations, 1988-2000
    - Symbol Technologies Nomination Letter, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - IEM Harvard University, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Mayor's Award (A.G. Schillinger) Nominated, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sub-series F: Technology in Society, 1974-2008
    - Fuglsang, Lars, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Golden, William T., 1974-1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Technology in Society, TASME & MOT Correspondence (1990) (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Technology in Society, TASME & MOT Correspondence (1991-1992) (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - TASME & Technology in Society Correspondence (1984-1985) (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Reserve Technology Institute (Mary Needham), 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - TIS Special Issue Retail, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Technology in Society Status & Organization Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Frank Davidson, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Sustainable Cities Issue Correspondence, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Anniversary Volume Correspondence, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Press Briefing & Luncheon, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Special Issue 1, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Special Issue 2, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - MacArthur Foundation (John D. & Catherine T.), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The Richard Dounsbery Foundation, 2002-2007 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Special Issue: China, India, and the US, 2004-2007 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Tony Wiener, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Elsevier Editors' Conference, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Advisory Board Letters, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Advisory Board (Miscellaneous), 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Advisory Board Invitations, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Advisory Board Lists, 1981-1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sub-series G: Yale University, 1980-1981
    - Technology, Management, and Policy - Yale, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Yale School of Management Correspondence (1980) (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - SOM/EAS Joint Program (Yale), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Technology: Management and Policy at Yale 2, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Yale '81, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Office of the Future (Yale), 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Yale University Position Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Yale University Executive Programs, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Yale University - Technology: Management and Policy Syllabus, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Report on Proposed Joint Management and Engineering Program at Yale University, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Technology: Management and Policy at Yale 1, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Series II: The American Society for Macro-Engineering, 1981-2005
  - Sub-series A: Administrative, 1983-2005
    - TASME - DOE Panel, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - TASME Dept. of Energy Transcript, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Press Release, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Notices for Meeting of Directors, 1983-2002 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Return Postcards, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - ASFME Master Mailing List, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Questionnaires, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Macro-Engineering Meeting, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Washington Chapter, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Membership Applications 1, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Master Mailing List, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Membership Applications 2, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - By-Laws of TASME, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors (TASME), 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - IAMES - Commission on Macro-Engineering, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sub-series B: Correspondence, 1981-2003
    - Communications to TASME, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Landis, John W. (1989- ) IAMES, 1990-2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Landis, J.W. (Correspondence '88), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Landis, J.W. (Correspondence 1987) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Landis, J.W. (Corresp. May-Dec '86), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Landis, J.W. (Corresp. Jan-Apr '86), 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Landis, J.W. (Correspondence '85), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - TASME, 1997-2002 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - TASME Correspondence (1982-1984) (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Ropes & Gray (Correspondence), 1982-1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (1985) (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Schillinger, A.G. (Corresp. Jan-Aug '85), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Schillinger, A.G. (Corresp. 1983) (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Schillinger, A.G. (Corresp. '81-'82), 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence ('82-'83), 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Early TASME Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - John Bloomer TASME Membership Request, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Schillinger, A.G. (Corresp. 1-6/86), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Schillinger, A.G. (Corresp. 7-12/86), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Schillinger, A.G. (Corres. Jan 1987) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Sub-series C: Drafts, Papers, and Publications, 2003-2005
    - TASME - 2002 Plus, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Sub-series D: Events and Conferences, 1983-1998
    - Conf. March 13-14, 86 Registration, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Conf. March 13-14, 86 Registration List, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Conf. March 13-14, 86 Checks, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Conf. (March 13-14, 86) Inquiries, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Plan for International Conference on Macro-Engineering (1987) (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Plan for International Conference on Macro-Engineering 1 (1986) (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Plan for International Conference on Macro-Engineering 2 (1986) (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - International TASME Meeting (1986), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Japan-America Student Conference, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Conf. March 13-14, 86 Accts., 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - TASME Conference Planning (1985-1986) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - MIT Apr. 29 Dinner 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Kick Off Dinner Invited Guests, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Ian Mac Gregor Speech 4/29/83, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - MIT Dinner PR Folder, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - MIT Dinner Agenda & Materials, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Mr. Masaki Nakajima Speech, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - MIT Dinner Agenda, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - World Science Center Workshop, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Conf. (March 13-14, 86) Cancellations, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Discounts/Press/Freebies, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Sub-series E: Financial, 1983-1997
    - Contributions 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - TASME Memberships 1992-1994 Copies of Invoices & Checks, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - ASFME Fin. Statements, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - IRS & NYS Taxes 1, 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - IRS & NYS Taxes 2, 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 1995 Bank Statements (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Canceled Checks & Related Expenses, 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - TASME Bank Statements (Copies) 1985-1996, 1985-1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Financial Statements, 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Sub-series F: Macro Projects, 1983-1990
    - Macro Projects - Current, 1983-09-23 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Macro News Clippings/Printed Matter, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Center for Macro Projects, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Smith-Richardson Foundation Proposal, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Clippings - Macro, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Sub-series G: Meeting Minutes, 1983-1996
    - TASME Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - TASME Minutes (1983-1996) (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - TASME Minutes, Correspondence & Proposals (1994-95), 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - TASME Minutes, Correspondence & Proposals '93/'94/'95, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - TASME Minutes, IAMES Conference (1994-96), 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Meeting Minutes, Member List (1990), Mailing List, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Meeting Minutes, Member List, Program Proposals, 1987-1990 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Meeting Minutes, Program Proposals, Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Objectives, Purposes, etc, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Sub-series H: Projects and Partnerships, 1981-1992
    - Proj. Performance Corp. (Corres), 1992 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Project Performance Corp. (Proposal Declined), 1992 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Project Performance Corp. (Travel Expenses), 1992 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Project Management Institute, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Mitsubishi, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Project Solutions Corporation Letter and Brochure, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Mitsubishi Research Institute, Inc., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Series III: Industrial Research Institute, 1978-1983
  - Sub-series A: Continuing Education, 1978-1981
    - Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Interviews, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - National Science Foundation Proposal, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Addresses 'New Directions in Continuing Education' Was Sent To, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sub-series B: Financial, 1978-1983
    - IRI/RC Finances (COMPER), 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Advanced Technology Management (Vouchers & Payment), 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sub-series C: Publications, 1981
    - Your Research and Development Career: A Study Guide For the First Five Years, 1981 (Box 6, Item 1)
- Series IV: Management of Technology, 1987-2007
  - Sub-series A: Administrative, 1990-1999
    - MOT Alumni, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - MOT Adjuncts, 1990-1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Purchasing Memento Gift and MOT Application Forms, 1997-03 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - MOT Grade Sheets (1997) (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - MOT 1996/97, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Call Log 1, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Call Log 2, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - MOT Student List 1992-1999 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Sub-series B: Correspondence and Memoranda, 1990-1998
    - Primot, Dominique Telecom Correspondence, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - Address Memos, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - MOT Correspondence (1990-1992) (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - MOT Class Speakers, 1991-1998 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Chang, David (President) Memorandum, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Sub-series C: Curriculum, 1989-1998
    - Syllabi and Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Childs (Seminar and Syllabus), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Lucent Technologies, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - MG866: Technology, Management and Policy, 1990-1993 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - MG870: Managerial Implications of Current Developments in Science & Tech, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - MG970: Business Policy, 1989-1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - MG 600 Spring & Sum 1990 Spring 1991, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - MG867: Technology Strategy, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - MG 870 MOT Spring '93, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - MG870 Spring '94, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - MG 86 Spring '97, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - MOT Program Survey, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Quantitative Methods Course Outline, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - MOT Spring '98, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - MG870 Spring '96, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - MG870 Spring '97, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - MG870 MOT Spring '98, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - MOT Fall '97, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - MG867 MOT Spring '98, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - MOT Class of '93, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - MG867 Spring '96, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - MOT Fall '95, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - MOT Class of '95, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - MOT Class of '96, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - MOT Syllabi Fall '94 Sp '95, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - MOT Syllabi 1996 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - MOT Class of '94, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Sub-series D: Evaluations, 1990-2007
    - Course Evaluations, Fall, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Donna Dufner, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - MG603 (B. David) Course Evaluation, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - MG609 (S. Kaplan) Course Evaluation, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - MG865 (A. Wiener) Course Evaluation, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - MG607 (L. Burkinshaw) Course Evaluation, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - MG736 (T. Freiser) Course Evaluation, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - MG820 (H. Rasmussen) Course Evaluation, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - (Course Evaluations) - 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - MOT Evaluations 1995, 1995-12-13 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - MOT Course Evaluations (1995) (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Dept. of Mgmt. Student's Confidential Course Evaluation, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Dept. of Management Fall 2007 Course Evaluations (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Dept. of Management Fall 2006 Course Evaluations (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - MOT (1991), 1990 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Course Evaluations (1994) (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Course Evaluations (1990-1993) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Sub-series E: Events and Conferences, 1991-1998
    - Bar-Cohen, Avram Ph.D. (MOT Panel), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Int'l Forum on Technology Management (November 3-7 1977) Kyoto, Japan, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - MOT Open House - July 31, 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - MOT Open House - June 22, 1994, 1994-06-22 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - MOT Open House - June 18, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - MOT Old Transparencies, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - MOT Open House - June 16, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - MOT Harvard Club Dinner (1992), 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - MOT Dinner (1993), 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - HC Graduation Dinner Class of 94, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - MOT Graduation Dinner (1995) (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - MOT Graduation Dinner (1996) (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - MOT Graduation Dinner (1997) (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - MOT Graduation Dinner - 1998 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Sub-series F: Financial, 1990-2001
    - MOT Budget F 93, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - MOT Budget F 90 F 91 F 92, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - MOT 1992/93, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - MOT Fiscal History, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Student Correspondence & Invoices, 1995-2001 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - MOT Budget FY '96, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Vouchers MOT - 9/90-9/91/92/93/94, 1990-1997 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Invoices and Expenditures (MOT), 1990-1998 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Kevin Smith ADC, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Sub-series G: Marketing, 1988-1998
    - Beekman Spring 1994 Mail Campaign (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - MOT Prospects, 1988-1992 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Beekman 1993 Campaign (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - MOT Special Letters, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - MOT Inquiries and Mailing List, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Final Market Research Results, 1997-04-01 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - MOT Advertising, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Stern and Stevens Executive Programs Cost, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - MOT Brochure & Diskette (1996) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - MOT Brochure (1996) and Application (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Registration & Orientation (1990) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - MOT Program Inquiries - (1990), 1989-1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Beekman 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Beekman '97, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Beekman 1996, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Ads, Press MOT, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Beekman '95, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - MOT Responses (1991) (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - MOT Request for Information, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Sub-series H: Program, 1987-1997
    - Proposal (State - MOT), 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - NY State Proposal, 1991-1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Audit for June 1997 MOT Candidates (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - MOT Notes, 1987-1992 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - MOT Questionnaire 1, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - MOT Questionnaire 2, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - MOT Questionnaire 3, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - MOT Class (1996) (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - MOT Registration Info, 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Chase IT, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Christopher Syvertsen MOT Enrollment/Resignation, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - MOT Unsuitable Applicants (1994) (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Smith, Kevin - Lotus Notes Questionnaire, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Series V: Brooklyn Poly, 1949-2008
  - Sub-series A: Academic Programs and Departments, 1970-2000
    - Appointments and Special Programs, 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - International Programs, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Strategic Alliances Prospectus, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Strategic Alliances, 1989-1992 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Richie Herink, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Forecasting Subcommit. Task Force 3 Folder 1 Reports, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Forecasting Subcommit. Task Force 3 Folder 2 Reports, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Executive Technical Development Brochures, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Exec. Sem. Oct 28-Nov 9. Part II, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Westchester Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Westchester Initial Programs, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Westchester-Master of Science Degree, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Westchester-Pace Management Science Grad. Program, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Westchester Petition to State Education Dept., 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Center for Technology in Supply Chains and Merchandising (Prospectus), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Advisory Committee (Mgmt. of Tech.), 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - AT&T Technical Education Center, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Feb 9, 1999 Focus Group (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Focus Group 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Luso-American Development Foundation, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sub-series B: Administrative, 1968-2006
    - AAUP Agreement, 1974-1980 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Code of Practice, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Faculty By-Laws, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Westchester Directions, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Westchester Company Index (1978) and ASTD List, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1985-1998 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - President's Advisory Council, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Intercampus Travel, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Change of Grade Request, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Personnel Action Form & Tuition Remission Form, 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Enrollment Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Mgt. Presentation, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 28)